O.k., now I have all my napkins separated.
I'm just going to push aside the four corners out of the way; but keep them where their going to be placed and we'll work on one corner at a time.
I like to do my decoupage by first putting a thin layer of the decoupage glue down first, and then adding more glue over; after.
So the first one is easy, you start it in the corner and place it carefully on the glue. And then just pat that down on the glue, o.k... And then do that, go all the way around.
Now you can also go ahead and put the top glue on first before you work on your next corner, or you can go and do all the corners and then put your glazing glue on the top.
O.k., now I'll show you how to join the two corners; again you want to put a very thin layer of the decoupage glue and work fast so it doesn't dry before you're finished.
And again you want to start at the corner and work your way down to the, where it's joined; o.k... Place that down and then just pat the napkin in place.
Now it's o.k. if the napkin wrinkles a bit, it gives it a little bit of an antiquey look and pat that in place.
And you can see that the napkin was translucent there and you do see the patterns, but because we've made a cut and kind of softened the cut you don't notice it at all.
And then you want to glaze over with the decoupage glue.
Now when your glazing over you want to be very careful that you have plenty of glue on your finger, and you just work very delicately because the napkin is so thin it's like a piece of tissue paper and when you wet it with the glue it's a wet piece of tissue paper; so it's very, very delicate.
And you want to work very gently with it.
And just make sure that your finger is always slick with glue, and don't let that glue dry out while you're working on it.
Just glaze that over.